=Afterlife of Love and Revenge= =Episode 7=
= الآخرة من الحب والانتقام = = الحلقة 7 =
How are we going to pay the debt?
كيف سنسدد الدين؟
The imperial examination is coming in another month.
الامتحان الإمبراطوري قادم في شهر آخر.
We can't even pay the debt.
لا يمكننا حتى سداد الديون.
How will we have the money for you to go to the capital?
كيف سيكون لدينا المال لتذهب إلى العاصمة؟
I heard that your sister and her husband
سمعت أن أختك وزوجها
have opened a medicine store in the market.
فتحت متجرًا للأدوية في السوق.
Their business is good.
عملهم جيد.
Why not
لما لا
you go and borrow money from her?
تذهب وتقترض منها المال؟
Her husband?
زوجها؟
Pang Shuangyue and Pei Jinheng
بانغ شوانجيو وباي جينهينغ
were having an affair at our place.
كانوا على علاقة غرامية في مكاننا.
Who else can she marry
من غيره يمكن أن تتزوج
if not him?
إن لم يكن هو؟
No need to look for her.
لا حاجة للبحث عنها.
I'll go to the market tomorrow with Qingmu
سأذهب إلى السوق غدًا مع Qingmu
and earn money with him.
وكسب المال معه.
What if you can't earn any money?
ماذا لو لم تتمكن من كسب أي أموال؟
If we can't earn any money...
إذا لم نتمكن من كسب أي أموال ...
If we can't earn any money, we won't come back.
إذا لم نتمكن من كسب أي أموال ، فلن نعود.
Okay.
تمام.
That's what you said.
هذا ما قلته انت.
Don't miss this!
لا تفوت هذا!
Miss,
يغيب،
do you need some medicine?
هل تحتاج الى بعض الادوية؟
Sir, buy some medicine.
سيدي ، اشتري بعض الأدوية.
We just dug this out.
لقد حفرنا هذا للتو.
Buy some.
شراء بعض.
It's not easy for you, dear.
ليس من السهل عليك يا عزيزي.
Wipe your sweat.
امسح عرقك.
Many people are looking at us.
كثير من الناس ينظرون إلينا.
No one is looking at us now.
لا أحد ينظر إلينا الآن.
Get out!
اخرج!
How do you buy medicine if you have no money?
كيف تشتري الدواء إذا لم يكن لديك نقود؟
(Pei Medicine Store) Get lost.
(متجر باي للأدوية) تضيع.
It's a misunderstanding.
إنه سوء فهم.
I just forgot to bring my wallet.
لقد نسيت فقط إحضار محفظتي.
The patient is dying now.
المريض يحتضر الآن.
I'll pay you afterward.
سأدفع لك بعد ذلك.
(Isn't that the Great Physician, Li?)
(أليس هذا الطبيب العظيم ، لي؟)
(In the previous lifetime, he healed Magistrate Zhang)
(في حياته السابقة ، شفى القاضي تشانغ)
(when he first came to Qingshui County.)
(عندما جاء لأول مرة إلى مقاطعة Qingshui.)
(He then became famous.)
(ثم ​​اشتهر).
I've seen many people like you.
لقد رأيت الكثير من الناس مثلك.
(I need to seize this opportunity.)
(أحتاج إلى اغتنام هذه الفرصة).
(Physician Li) If you're not paying,
(الطبيب لي) إذا كنت لا تدفع ،
I'll break your legs.
(الطبيب لي)
Stop it.
توقف عن ذلك.
I'm not a swindler.
أنا لست محتالاً.
Look.
نظرة.
Longyue.
لونجيوي.
It's been a while.
لقد مر وقت طويل.
How much is he owing you?
كم هو مدين لك؟
Do you have money?
هل لديك المال؟
Isn't that just noble dendrobium?
أليس هذا مجرد ديندروبيوم نوبل؟ Isn't that just noble dendrobium؟
We have it, too.
لدينا ذلك أيضًا.
If you need it urgently for your patient,
إذا كنت في حاجة ماسة إليه لمريضك ،
take these first.
خذ هذه أولا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Qingmu, you're generous.
تشينغمو ، أنت كريم.
I heard that you're in heavy debt.
سمعت أنك مدين بالديون الثقيلة.
So, I thought you're not having a good life.
لذلك ، اعتقدت أنك لا تتمتع بحياة جيدة.
I'm not sure if you're having a good life,
لست متأكدًا مما إذا كنت تتمتع بحياة جيدة ،
but
لكن
we're living a good life.
نحن نعيش حياة جيدة.
You're just lying.
أنت تكذب فقط.
I wish your business prospers.
أتمنى أن يزدهر عملك.
Thank you for helping me.
شكرا لمساعدتي.
After I treated the patient,
بعد أن عالجت المريض ،
I'll pay you.
سوف ادفع لك.
(The Second Day)
(اليوم الثاني)
Come and see!
تعال وشاهد!
This is good medicine!
هذا دواء جيد!
Sir, take a look.
سيدي الق نظرة.
Swindler!
المحتال!
After taking your medicine,
بعد تناول دوائك ،
I was vomiting and having diarrhea.
كنت أتقيأ وأصاب بالإسهال.
I almost died.
لقد كنت على وشك الموت.
How can it be? We haven't even started selling anything.
كيف يمكن أن يكون؟  لم نبدأ حتى في بيع أي شيء.
Everyone, come here!
الجميع ، تعالوا إلى هنا!
They don't admit that they're selling fake medicine.
لا يعترفون بأنهم يبيعون أدوية مزيفة.
It's you who sold me the medicine.
أنت من باع لي الدواء.
You're being ridiculous.
كنت يجري سخيفة.
You're speaking loudly even after taking our fake medicine.
أنت تتحدث بصوت عالٍ حتى بعد تناول أدويتنا المزيفة.
It seems like our medicine is great.
يبدو أن دوائنا رائع.
You're being ridiculous.
كنت يجري سخيفة.
I can prove that
يمكنني إثبات ذلك
Magistrate Zhang is recovering
القاضي تشانغ يتعافى
after taking their medicine.
بعد تناول الدواء.
Their medicine is real.
طبهم حقيقي.
Why are you framing them?
لماذا تقوم بتأطيرهم؟
Isn't this Physician Li?
أليس هذا الطبيب لي؟
Physician Li?
الطبيب لي؟
That's him.
انه هو.
I've met him before.
لقد التقيت به من قبل.
I want to buy some medicine!
أريد شراء بعض الأدوية!
- Me too!
- أنا أيضاً!  - أنا أيضاً!
- Give me one!
- أعطني واحدة!  - أعطني واحدة!
Okay, please line up.
حسنًا ، من فضلك اصطف.
You're useless.
أنت عديم الفائدة.
Don't push. We have more.
لا تدفع.  لدينا المزيد.
Send a letter to Zhao Baidou.
إرسال بريد إلكتروني إلى Zhao Baidou.
Thank you, everyone.
شكرا لكل شخص.
Just tell him
فقط أخبره
I want to meet him.
أريد مقابلته.
♪You're the fated love coming from the immortal world♪
أنت الحب المقدّر الآتي من العالم الخالد
♪You tie the red strings on the tips of my fingers♪
♪ تقوم بربط الخيوط الحمراء على أطراف أصابعي ♪
♪My heart won't change even if time passes♪
♪ قلبي لن يتغير حتى لو مر الوقت
♪I'll wait for the love in the old place as promised♪
♪ سأنتظر الحب في المكان القديم كما وعدت ♪